<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oliver Hough</title>
    <link>https://oliverhough.cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Oliver Hough</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 10:23:15 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://oliverhough.cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinkys Palace V1</title>
      <link>https://oliverhough.cloud/writeups/pinkys-palace-v1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 10:23:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oliverhough.cloud/writeups/pinkys-palace-v1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Today we are going to look at how I solved the Pinky&amp;rsquo;s Palace V1 Boot2Root from VulnHub. I really enjoyed this box and would recommend it for anyone who wants to practice common exploitation methods.
VM Info Name: Pinky&amp;rsquo;s Palace V1
Author: @Pink_P4nther
Link: https://www.vulnhub.com/entry/pinkys-palace-v1,225
Difficulty: Beginner / Intermediate
Networking: Auto DHCP (192.168.1.45)
Discovery We begin our journey with a port scan. The VM tells us it&amp;rsquo;s IP on boot so we don&amp;rsquo;t need to go and scan our own network to find the host, in my case the IP is 192.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breach Hunting 101</title>
      <link>https://oliverhough.cloud/blog/breach-hunting-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 22:37:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oliverhough.cloud/blog/breach-hunting-101/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I hope this article can give you a basic introduction to the world of &amp;lsquo;breach hunting&amp;rsquo; something I have recently come to enjoy (wierd right?). This is by no means an exhaustive list of tools and methodologies but more a primer to get you going in the exhilarating world of spending hours trawling through other peoples lists, spreadsheets and datasets for the greater good.
Searching With all the different methods I find it is more manageable to split my searches by country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Pi-Hole with DNS Over HTTPS</title>
      <link>https://oliverhough.cloud/blog/configure-pihole-with-dns-over-https/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 20:57:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oliverhough.cloud/blog/configure-pihole-with-dns-over-https/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Today CloudFlare launched 1.1.1.1, a new consumer DNS resolver that promises to respect your privacy, it also supports DNS over HTTPS! I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of Pi-Hole which I use to block tracking, advertisements etc across my whole network but unfortunately Pi-Hole does not yet support DNS over HTTPS. Lucky for us CloudFlare have released a https proxy which we can use while we wait for Pi-Hole to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using AWS s3 Bucket Policies</title>
      <link>https://oliverhough.cloud/blog/using-aws-bucket-policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 11:57:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oliverhough.cloud/blog/using-aws-bucket-policies/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you have not been living in a dark disconnected cave for the past year, you may have noticed the growing trend of abusing badly configured Amazon s3 buckets for fun and profit. Using tools like Bucket Stream and Teh S3 Bucketeers for a short time you&amp;rsquo;ll see how bad the situation really is.
Check Your Bucket ACL and Bucket Policy You can check your bucket ACL using the folowing command ( more info on AWS CLI )</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>